Privacy Policy
--------------

MPS Limited and all of its subsidiary companies (together “MPS”) respects your concerns about privacy and values its relationship with you. This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) describes:

* the types of information we collect from customers, contacts and visitors to our website at www.highwirepress.com
* how we may use that information
* with whom we may share that information; and
* the measures we take to protect the security of that information.

### **Data Controller and Data Processor**

We process two main types of personal data.

1. **Customer Data –** Personal data that forms part of data that is provided by our customers and their end-users for processing.
2. **Other Data –** Personal data about our customers, visitors and other individuals that is collected and processed directly by us.

Our Customers are the Controller of **Customer Data**.

MPS is the processor of **Customer Data** and the Controller of **Other Data**.

### **Information We Collect and How We Use It**

MPS collects, processes, and retains information about you when you visit our website if you choose to provide. You may choose to provide some of this information directly, such as when you submit the “Contact Us” form or any other registration forms. We use the contact information we collect to respond to your enquiry or to allow you to access specific account information. We may execute other activities, such as marketing campaigns, promotional communications for which consent is taken appropriately, or another appropriate lawful base for which the processing is identified.

You may visit our website without telling us who you are. When you visit our website, our web servers or our analytics services collect IP addresses, operating system details, browsing details, device details, and language settings. This information is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, and similar information. MPS uses this information to measure the site usage, improve content, and ensure safety and security as well enhance the performance of the website.

You can make choices about our collection and use of your data. You may decline when you are asked to provide personal data. The data that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with MPS and the choices you make, including your privacy settings. We collect your first name, last name, phone number, email address, job title, company, state, region, and other information.

### **Personal Information We Collect About You**

You may choose to provide personal information (such as your name, address, telephone number and email address) to us. We list below the methods by which you may provide the information and the types of information you may submit. We also tell you how we may use the information.

### **Contact Us**

If you communicate with our Customer Services department through the ‘Contact Us’ link on our website or by post or telephone, we may ask you for information such as your email address, your location and the type of customer you are (e.g. registrant, website visitor etc.). You may also choose to provide additional personal information, for example, in the form of an attachment or by post. We will hold these details in our customer services query database and use such personal information to respond to your questions and comments. We may also use such personal information to evaluate the quality of our products and services.

### **Work @ MPS Limited**

You may submit your CV and other information online through our careers page to apply for a job with MPS. We use the information you submit to evaluate your suitability for the position and to contact you regarding your application. It may be that some of the Personal Data you give us (for instance about your lifestyle or health) is sensitive personal data within the meaning of the General Data Protection Regulation.

### **Other Website Features**

We offer website visitors various features for their information, which we may change from time to time. We may ask you to submit certain personal information so we can provide you with these features.

### **Other Uses of Information**

We may use the personal information you provide on our website for internal purposes, such as for website administration, data analytics and compliance purposes.

### **Users under 18 years of age**

The Sites and Services do not knowingly collect personal information from users under the age of 18.

If you are under the age of 18, you are not permitted to use the Sites and Services or to disclose Personal Information. If we learn we have collected or received Personal Information from a child under 18, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact us.

### **Blogs and Other Public Forums**

The Site makes blogs and other such user-generated content facilities available to users of the Site, and registered users can provide content for and participate in these facilities. Any information that is disclosed in these areas of our Site becomes public information, and you should always be careful when deciding to disclose your personal information.

When you use this facility and provide us with personal data of a third party (e.g., a name and email address), please ensure that you have that party’s consent before giving us these details.

### **Non-personal Information We Collect**

We collect certain aggregated and non-personal information when you visit our website. Aggregated and non-personal information does not relate to a single, identifiable visitor. Instead, it tells us such information as how many users visited our website and which pages were accessed. By collecting this information, we learn how to best tailor our website to our visitors. We collect this information either through “cookie” technology or with “web beacons,” as explained below.

### **Cookies**

We use cookies for some of our website(s). However, to optimize our website’s efficiency, we use other identifiers to gather usage and performance data. We mainly use GTM/GA ([read Google’s privacy policy](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245)) to count the number of unique visitors to a web page or service and to develop other statistics about the operations of our website

### **Web Beacons**

Certain pages on our website contain “web beacons” (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags, and clear GIFs or java script equivalents). These web beacons allow third parties to obtain such information as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page, and the information in cookies set by the third party.

### **Information We Share**

MPS uses your data to protect the security and safety of our website. We use these data to communicate with you and personalize our messages. You can sign up for email subscriptions and choose whether you wish to receive promotional communications from MPS by email, SMS, mail, and telephone about managing your contact data. Also, you have a right to withdraw consent at any time for future processing, you have the right to object to the processing of your personal data.

We do not sell or otherwise disclose information about our website visitors, except as described here. We may share the information you provide with affiliates of MPS (i.e., companies in our group) and our joint marketing partners. We may also share the information with service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf. These service providers are not authorized by us to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements. In addition, we may disclose information about you:

(i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process,

(ii) to law enforcement agencies following an appropriate request, or

(iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity.

We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use information you have provided through our website(s) in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

### **How We Protect Personal Information**

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against loss, misuse or unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of the information you provide on our website.

### **Data Retention**

We will retain your personal information for as long as is needed to fulfil the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting or other legal requirements).

MPS will retain Customer Data in accordance with a customer’s instructions, including any applicable terms in the Customer Agreement and as required by applicable law. When you decide to close your account, we delete all personal information about you.

MPS may retain other information, including information that you provide to us, for as long as necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

### **Your Rights to Control Data**

Whenever you use our services, we aim to provide you easy means to access, modify, delete, object to or restrict use of your personal information.

MPS will provide website users with access to a copy of their personal information which they have provided through our site(s), where such users are reasonably entitled to ask for this, (for which we may charge a small fee not exceeding the statutory maximum) and they will have the ability to review and correct it, as applicable. You can ask us to erase or delete all or some of your personal data (e.g., if it is no longer necessary to provide Services to you). You can ask us to stop using all or some of your personal data (e.g., if we have no legal right to keep using it) or to limit our use of it (e.g., if your personal data is inaccurate or unlawfully held).

To help protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity, such as requiring a password and user ID, before granting access to your information.

### **Cross-Border Data Transfers**

Since we are an international company, your data will be processed outside of the EU region within Third Party Data Centers.

If information you provided includes personal information of individuals based within or outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”), you agree to obtain express consent, whenever required under the applicable law, from these individuals prior to the submission of such personal information to MPS. If information you provided includes personal information of individuals within the China, you agree and warrant to notify these individuals of such cross border transfer and obtain separate consent from these individuals, whenever required under the applicable laws, prior to the submission of such personal information to MPS. By consenting to this Privacy Statement, you confirm that explicit consent has been obtained from the relevant individuals.

### **Your Choices**

If you would like to update your contact information and preferences or would like to be removed from our mailing list, you may email us at [dpo@mpslimited.com](mailto:dpo@mpslimited.com).

### **Updates to Our Privacy POLICY**

This Policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our online information practices. We will post a prominent notice on this site to notify you of any significant changes to our Policy and indicate at the top of the Policy when it was most recently updated.

### **How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or comments about this Notice, or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us by:

* Sending an email to Data Protection Officer: [dpo@mpslimited.com](mailto:dpo@mpslimited.com)
* Writing to:

HMG Ambassador  
5th Floor  
137 Residency Road  
Bangalore – 560025  
India

MPS Limited is a limited liability company registered with the Registrar of Companies.  
Head office:  
MPS Limited  
4th Floor, Tower – A,  
Windsor IT Park, A-1,  
Sector 125, Noida,  
Uttar Pradesh, 201 303,  
INDIA  
Company Reg No: 05795

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area and we maintain your Personal Data within the scope of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you have additional rights.  If you are not satisfied with the resolution, you can also lodge a complaint with the Supervisory Authority in the country of your residence

**_Last Updated – 24/12/2021_**
